The ultimate female who used her beauty and her body to bring
kingdoms to their downfall and men to their knees!
The Vengeance of She is a adventure, fantasy film directed by Cliff Owen.
Beautiful young European girl, Carol, is possessed by the spirit of Ayesha – “She Who Must be
Obeyed” – and led to the lost city of Kuma, where she is destined to become queen.
Killikrates, played by John Richardson.
Carol / Ayesha, played by Olga Schoberová.
Philip, played by Edward Judd.
George, played by Colin Blakely.
Sheila, played by Jill Melford.
Harry, played by George Sewell.
The Vengeance of She is a 1968 British fantasy film directed by Cliff Owen and starring
John Richardson, Olinka Berova, Edward Judd, André Morell, and Colin Blakely.
It has little in common with the 1905 novel Ayesha: The Return of She by H.
Rider Haggard.
It was made by Hammer Films as a loose sequel to the 1965 hit film She.
The film explores themes of beauty, sequel, lost city, possesion.